Joseph L. Rauh Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part I: Subject File, 1944-1988 (Box 20-45)
  - Passports
    - 1958-1962
    - 1953-1958 (Box 39)
  - Pensions, House of Representatives rankings, 1978
  - Philippines, 1945-1948
  - Poff, Richard H., Supreme Court nomination, 1971
  - Presidential campaigns
    - 1980
    - 1976
      - Clippings
      - General
    - 1972
    - 1968
    - 1960
  - Progressive, 1950-1968
  - Rehnquist, William H., Supreme Court nominations
    - Associate justice, 1971, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - Chief justice, 1986, (2 folders)
  - Reinhold Niebuhr Award, Inc., fund, 1972-1975 (Box 41)
  - Reuther, Walter P., 1949, 1954-1965, 1970
  - Roy Wilkins Memorial Foundation, 1984-1985
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier (1917- ), 1949-1972, (3 folders)
  - School Desegregation Act of 1961, 1960-1961
  - School segregation, 1956-1961
  - Shipley, Carl L., 1954, 1963
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare, 1947
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (1930- ), 1952-1957, (2 folders)
  - Supreme Court, limitation of appellate jurisdiction, 1958-1959 (Box 42)
  - Tidelands oil case, 1946-1948
  - Tokyo Rose, presidential pardon, 1975-1976
  - “Union democracy”
    - 1983-1985, (2 folders)
    - 1958-1981, (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Union for Democratic Action, 1946
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1985-1986
  - United States Senate, rule 22, filibuster rule
    - 1958-1975, (3 folders)
    - 1950-1957, (4 folders) (Box 44)
  - Wallace, Henry Agard, 1945-1947
  - White, Harry Dexter, 1953-1954, 1965, (3 folders) (Box 45)
  - Miscellany, 1963-1985
- Part I: Legal File, 1940-1986 (Box 46-202)
  Correspondence, depositions, memoranda, briefs, writs, petitions, photographs, reports, transcripts, and printed matter pertaining to Rauh's legal cases.
  Arranged alphabetically by case name, client name, or subject, with the majority of the files further arranged by topic or type of material. Miscellaneous briefs, writs, and committee prints are arranged alphabetically by case name, client name, or subject.
  - Abood, D. Louis, 1975-1977, (3 folders) (Box 46)
  - Adams, Frances, 1970-1971
  - Adams v. City of Detroit, 1972-1973, (2 folders)
  - AFL-CIO, 1970
  - Alaska pipeline case
    - 1976
    - 1974-1975, (4 folders) (Box 47)
  - Alcohol and Drug Problems Association of North America, 1963, 1970-1976
  - Alleghany Corp.
    - Court of Appeals notes, John Silard
    - District Court, 1959-1960
    - General, 1956-1965, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Knudsen materials, copies of, 1954-1959
    - Memoranda of facts and supporting documents, 1954-1955
    - Working papers
      - 1959-1960
      - 1959 (Box 49)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Council 21, 1971-1973, 1979, (3 folders)
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists
    - Briefs, writs, and petitions, 1973-1975, (2 folders)
    - General, 1974-1976 (Box 50)
  - American Psychoanalytic Association, 1968
  - American University v. Strauss, 1969
  - Amison, George E., 1969-1970
  - Bachowski, Walter, 1974-1976, (2 folders)
  - Bandoni, Joseph P., 1962-1969
  - Bannockburn, 1969 (Box 51)
  - Barnes, Roland E.
    - Depositions, 1962-1966, (2 folders)
    - General, 1961-1971, (5 folders)
    - Work file, 1962-1964 (Box 52)
  - Barus, David N., 1976
  - Beasley, Thomas B. and Willie T., 1951-1956
  - Beck v. Communications Workers, 1980
  - Bedell, Steven, 1967-1969
  - Benda v. Grand Lodge of International Association of Machinists, 1977-1978
  - Bernstein, Charles, 1940-1943, 1958-1968, (2 folders)
  - Bernstein, Stephanie, 1975-1976
  - Bipartisan Committee on Absentee Voting, Alfred E. Davidson, 1967-1972
  - Block, Herb, 1975 (Box 53)
  - Booth, Jerry H., 1972
  - Boyle, Kay, 1977-1983
  - Breth, Jennings Herrick, 1966-1967
  - Bricklayers Union No. 4, 1972
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
    - Briefs and petitions
      - Bangor and Aroostock Railroad Co., (3 folders) (Box 54)
      - Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co., (3 folders) (Box 55)
      - Miscellany
    - General, 1971 (Box 56)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks (Ellis/Fails)
    - Briefs, 1981-1983
    - Correspondence
      - 1977-1985, (5 folders)
      - 1975-1976, (3 folders) (Box 57)
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1952-1965, (2 folders)
  - Brown, Ralph D., 1968
  - Buchanan, Bernice F., 1968-1969
  - Buchanan, Martha Helene, 1972-1973
  - Buck, Carl H.
    - Board for Correction of Naval Records, 1956-1959
    - Briefs and decisions, 1952-1954
    - Court of Claims, 1959-1962
    - Court of Military Appeals, 1954-1959 (Box 58)
    - Discharge, unjust, 1956-1959
    - Evidence, newly discovered, 1952-1959
    - General
      - 1957-1967, (5 folders)
      - 1952-1956, (2 folders) (Box 59)
    - Pardon petition
      - Exhibits, 1959
      - General, 1959
    - Statements, 1953-1957
    - Work file, 1952-1959, (2 folders)
  - Burton, Lola M. See Container 67, same heading
  - Burmese case, U Aung Than/BoSetKya, 1966-1967
  - Campbell, Donald F., 1970-1971
  - Campus Americans for Democratic Action, low-cost standby youth fares (Box 60)
    - Briefs filed by others, 1970
    - General, 1966-1970, (2 folders)
  - Carey, James B., 1965-1967
  - Carr, James H., 1964-1965
  - Carroll, Peter J., Jr., 1970-1971
  - Carter v. Carey, 1964
  - Cigich, Joseph M., 1969-1970 (Box 61)
  - Clark, Grenville, 1963-1964
  - Clark, Joseph S., 1967-1970
  - Clark v. Clark, 1967-1968
  - Colonial Penn Group, Inc., 1976-1978, (2 folders)
  - Coy, Grace C., 1967
  - Cutler, Wallace, 1959-1963
  - Dargusch, Carlton (Box 62)
    - Disbarment proceeding, 1964-1965
    - General, 1965
  - Deerfield Park District v. Progress Development Corp.
    - 1962-1963, (3 folders)
    - 1959-1961, (3 folders) (Box 63)
  - Democratic Party, challenge of delegates by George McGovern
    - 1972, (2 folders)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 64)
  - District of Columbia, mass transit and freeways, 1969
  - Djilas, Milovan, 1957-1958
  - Donath, Ludwig, 1958
  - Donovan, Thomas A., 1966-1967
  - Douglas, Mercedes, 1963-1966
  - Dowling, Monroe D.
    - 1976-1978
    - 1975, (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Drew, Grace
    - General, 1964-1968, (2 folders)
    - Notes and exhibits used at trial, 1968
  - Ellinger, W. Don, 1962-1964
  - Erenreich, Dorothea, 1960-1964, (3 folders) (Box 66)
  - Evans, George E., 1952-1965, (2 folders)
  - Ewing, Mrs. M. H., 1961-1962 (Box 67)
  - Farber, Martin A., 1960-1961
  - Farm Workers Action Committee, 1969
  - Ferguson, Dolores, and Lola M. Burton, 1964
  - Fertig, Ralph, 1969
  - Fleming, Harold C., 1959-1963, (2 folders)
  - Forrest Industries, Inc., 1968-1969
  - Frankforther, Robert L., 1969
  - Freedman, Monroe, 1966
  - Friedman, Robert Samuel, 1965-1966
  - Galarza v. Di Giorgio, 1963-1966 (Box 68)
  - Gallo boycott case, 1974, (2 folders)
  - Gardner, Thelma G., 1963
  - Gichner, Lawrence E., 1963-1964
  - Gleason, Joseph D., 1968-1969
  - Greenwich Institute, proposed, 1968 (Box 69)
  - Greer, Juanita M., 1969
  - Griffin v. Maryland, 1958-1963, (4 folders)
  - Hall, Robert, 1957-1964, (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Hammond, Joseph, 1954-1962, (3 folders)
  - Hardy, Mrs. Willie, 1962-1964
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1950-1986, (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Herring, Helen M., 1967
  - Hohri, William, 1967-1986, (3 folders)
  - Hughes, Paul H., 1956-1958
  - Ighnat, Betty Jane, 1967-1969 (Box 72)
  - Independent Socialist League
    - Correspondence, 1956-1958
    - General, 1956-1958
    - Listing as a communist organization, 1949-1958, (2 folders)
    - Shachtman, Max
      - 1955-1957
      - 1952-1954, (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - "Indian tribe, Sisseton-Wahpeton Sioux," 1968
  - Jackson, Gardner, 1947, 1955-1957, 1965-1967
  - Jamaica Broadcasting Corp., 1964
  - Jenrette, John W.
    - Briefs
      - 1984, (2 folders)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 74)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985
    - Transcripts
      - 1980
        - Sept. 5-9, (2 folders)
        - Sept. 10-17, (4 folders) (Box 75)
        - Sept. 18-22, (3 folders) (Box 76)
        - Sept. 23-29, (5 folders) (Box 77)
        - Sept. 30-Oct. 3, (4 folders) (Box 78)
        - Oct. 6-Nov. 13, (4 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1981
        - Feb. 10
        - Feb. 11-May 15, (5 folders) (Box 80)
        - May 18-Sept. 22, (2 folders) (Box 81)
  - Johnson, Victor William, annuity benefits suit, 1954-1961, (2 folders)
  - Kaplan, Jacob M., motion picture, 1973-1974
  - Kelsey v. Weinberger, 1973 (Box 82)
  - Kish, Leslie, 1971-1972
  - Kuhn, Katherine Vail, 1980-1983
  - Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1958-1961
  - Lassar, Richard E., 1969-1970
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1965-1977, (2 folders)
  - Leon, Arnold, 1960-1964
  - Lepscky, Carlo, 1961-1962
  - Leverton, Lillian M., 1969-1970
  - Levin, Arthur J. (Box 83)
    - General, 1965
    - Work file, 1963-1966
  - Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Co., 1968-1969
  - Linebaugh, David, 1974
  - Machinists
    - Bribery, 1976-1978
    - Coordinated bargaining, 1978
    - Freedom of information appeal, 1978-1979
    - Labor board, 1978-1979
    - Lobbying, gas bill, 1978
    - Pension fund, 1979-1980
  - Mack, Marvin D., 1964-1968 (Box 84)
  - Macon v. American Federation of Government Employees
    - General, 1970-1972
    - Pleadings file, 1972
  - McCarthy, Eugene J., equal time case, 1967-1968, (2 folders)
  - McGraw, B. T., 1969
  - MCHR, addresses and telephone numbers, 1978-1979
  - McLean Gardens, 1961
  - Meyers, Melville, 1967-1969
  - Miller, Arthur See also Container 274, same heading (Box 85)
    - Court of Appeals, 1957-1960, (2 folders)
    - Passports
  - Miners for Democracy, 1971-1973 (Box 86)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party
    - Briefs, 1964-1965
    - General, 1960-1972, 1980, (4 folders)
  - Moi, Tang Tchong (Danny), 1958, 1964-1966
  - Motor carrier safety, 1970-1971
  - Muchnik, Jacobo, 1956, 1962-1971 (Box 87)
  - National Football League Players Association
    - Citations
    - Clippings, 1980
    - General
      - 1981-1984, (2 folders)
      - 1980
        - Nov.-Dec.
        - Apr.-Nov., (2 folders) (Box 88)
  - Orlikow v. United States, 1986 See also Containers 217-268, 274-282, and 287, same heading, (2 folders)
  - Outer Continental Shelf
    - Contract, 1980-1982
    - General
      - 1980-1981
      - 1977-1979, (2 folders) (Box 89)
    - General correspondence, 1978-1982, (3 folders)
    - Indexes
    - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1980
    - Pleadings (Box 90)
      - Bound (fastners removed by library staff)
        - June 1979-May 1981, (4 folders)
        - June 1981-Nov. 1982, (3 folders) (Box 91)
      - Unbound
        - 1980-1981, (3 folders)
        - 1978-1980, (2 folders) (Box 92)
    - Transcripts, 1979-1981
    - Miscellany, 1979-1981
  - Philby, Eleanor K., 1964-1965 (Box 93)
  - Powell, Yvette Flores (Mrs. Adam Clayton Powell (1908-1972), 1967-1972
  - Project on Budget Priorities, undated
  - Quaker Action Group
    - 1973-1977, (4 folders)
    - 1970-1973, (4 folders) (Box 94)
    - 1968-1969, (3 folders) (Box 95)
  - Reis, Pat, 1971-1977
  - Ringer v. Mumford
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974
    - Pleadings file
      - 1971-1972
      - 1972-1973 (Box 96)
  - Seay v. McDonnell Douglas Corp., 1974-1977
  - Slaiman, Donald, 1948-1962
  - Sobell, Morton, 1957-1963
  - Sollins, I. V., 1970-1971
  - Taylor, Mark F., 1968-1972
  - Texaco, Inc., rights of accused employees in disciplinary investigations, 1968-1969 (Box 97)
  - United Auto Workers, AFL/CIO See also Container 282, same heading
    - Bombings, 1962, 1968
    - Border crossing, 1949-1967
    - Brooks Research and Manufacturing, 1972-1973
    - "B" miscellaneous, 1961-1964, 1971
    - Chicago Stamping Plant, Ford Motor Co., 1977-1978
    - Civil rights
      - Birmingham, Ala., bail bonds, 1963-1972, (3 folders)
      - Democratic Party, African American adherence to, 1963 (Box 98)
      - Demonstrations, 1963
      - Part III of Act, 1963
    - Civil rights and civil liberties, 1953-1962, (3 folders)
    - Committee for National Insurance, 1969-1973, (2 folders)
    - Communications Satellite Corp., 1962
    - Communism, 1961-1962, 1968
    - Convention, 1964
    - "C" miscellaneous, 1963-1968
    - Dayton-Columbus amicus brief, 1979
    - Debt assistance for unemployed workers, 1962
    - Deductibility of union dues, Internal Revenue Service code regulations, 1959-1960 (Box 99)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt Foundation, 1963
    - Ex-Cell-O
      - Briefs, 1967, (2 folders)
      - General, 1967-1970
      - United States Court of Appeals
        - 1971-1976, (2 folders)
        - 1970 (Box 100)
    - Exempt organizations, 1963
    - "E" miscellaneous, 1963-1967
    - Fafnir Bearing Co.
      - 1963-1967, (3 folders)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 101)
    - Free Labor Cooperative Education Fund, 1962
    - Fringe benefits, 1963
    - "F" miscellaneous, 1963-1967
    - General, 1956, 1967
    - General Counsel, 1963-1967
    - General Motors Corp.
      - Agency shop, 1961-1963, (3 folders)
      - Price profit charge of 1961, 1957-1962, (2 folders) (Box 102)
      - Salaried workers, 1963-1964
      - Subcontracting, 1964-1967
      - Supreme Court
        - Briefs, 1962-1963
        - Work file, 1962-1963 (Box 103)
    - Goodman, Leo, 1967-1969
    - Gosser, Richard, 1962-1963
    - Gray v. Reuther, 1960, (2 folders)
    - Group Research, Inc., 1962-1963
    - Group Research, Inc. v. Waite, 1968-1970
    - Hartwell, Ga., Monroe Shock Absorber Co., 1963-1966, (2 folders)
    - Hoosier Cardinal Corp., 1965-1966
    - Hughes Tool Co., 1963-1964, (2 folders) (Box 104)
    - "H" miscellaneous, 1958-1966
    - Industrial personnel security program, 1948-1960, (3 folders)
    - Industrial Union Department, 1962-1965 (Box 105)
    - International Union of Electrical Workers, 1963-1965
    - Karam, Barbara, 1959-1960
    - Kohler Co.
      - Court of Appeals
        - General
          - 1961-1965, (3 folders)
          - 1960, (3 folders) (Box 106)
        - Pleadings--joint appendix
          - Vol. 1
          - Vols. 2-4, (3 folders) (Box 107)
          - Vol. 5 (Box 108)
          - Supplemental
      - General, 1951-1957
      - Reinstatement of seventy-seven dischargees, 1964-1968
      - Supreme Court
        - Briefs and writs, 1954-1965, (1 folder) (Box 109)
        - General, 1961
    - Labor union idea, 1965-1966
    - Legal memoranda, 1963-1969
    - Legislation, 1960-1965
    - Levy, Leon, 1966-1969
    - Libel suit, Calore v. Gibson, 1963-1964
    - Lobbying act, 1956, 1963
    - Local Number 5, drug buying plan, 1962
    - Maschhoff, Jack, 1965
    - McCulloch Corp., 1964-1966, (3 folders) (Box 110)
    - McMillan, Homer, 1965-1969
    - Mields, Jennifer Robin, 1969 Restricted
    - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, International Union of, 1962-1965
    - Missiles, 1960-1965, (4 folders) (Box 111)
    - Multiunion bargaining units, article XXI, 1963-1964
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1961-1966
    - "N" miscellaneous, 1966-1967
    - Political contributions, 1956
    - PRDC (Monroe Reactor), 1963
    - Railway Clerks v. Allen, 1963-1964
    - Right to work case (Box 112)
      - Briefs and petitions, 1974-1984, (4 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1983-1985, (2 folders)
        - 1974-1982, (7 folders) (Box 113)
        - 1971-1973, (2 folders) (Box 114)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1975-1983
      - Plaintiff unions, communications to, 1975-1985
      - Plaintiff's motion for summary judgment
    - "R" miscellaneous, 1961-1970
    - United States Senate, rule 22
      - Complaint, original, 1980-1981
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979
      - Lawsuit, 1979
    - Williams, Fred (Box 115)
      - Board of Immigration Appeals hearings, 1961-1966, (2 folders)
      - British government letters, 1960
      - General, 1958-1966, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany of briefs, writs, and petitions, 1948-1971, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - United Mine Workers See also Container 282, same heading
    - Clippings, 1973-1975
    - Correspondence, 1971-1975
    - Foundations, 1970-1973
    - General, 1973
    - Legal papers, 1971-1977 (Box 117)
    - Miners for Democracy, 1972-1976
    - Miscellany, 1946, 1967-1977, (4 folders) (Box 118)
  - United Shoeworkers of America
    - Bata Shoe Co.
      - Briefs and petitions, 1966-1967
      - General, 1970-1971 (Box 119)
    - Brooks Shoe Manufacturing Co., (2 folders)
    - Brown Counter Co.
      - General, 1970-1974, (2 folders)
      - Tariff Commission, 1970-1972
    - General
      - 1973-1976
      - 1964-1972 (Box 120)
    - Hanover Shoe Co., 1969-1971, (3 folders)
    - Local bylaws
      - 1960-1968
      - 1959 (Box 121)
    - Merger, 1956-1957
    - Opinions, 1950-1971
    - Selis Shoe Repairing Co., 1971
    - Thurmont Shoe Co., 1969, (2 folders)
  - United Steelworkers of America
    - District director elections, 1973
    - McBride v. Sadlowski, 1977
  - United Steelworkers of America v. Rodriguez, 1976-1977 (Box 122)
  - United Steelworkers of America v. Sadlowski See also Container 282, same heading
    - Constitutions of United Steelworkers, 1972-1976
    - Department of Labor
      - Canadian investigation of election, 1977
      - Preelection correspondence, 1976-1977
    - Depositions
      - 1978, (3 folders)
      - 1974-1978, (5 folders) (Box 123)
    - Election day information suit, 1976-1977 (Box 124)
    - Exhibits, (3 folders)
    - General
      - 1983
      - 1981-1983, (5 folders) (Box 125)
      - 1979-1981, (5 folders) (Box 126)
      - 1979, (4 folders) (Box 127)
      - 1977-1978, (5 folders) (Box 128)
      - 1974-1977, (5 folders) (Box 129)
      - 1973-1974, (5 folders) (Box 130)
    - Gottesman and postelection protest correspondence, 1977 (Box 131)
    - McBride campaign literature, 1976
    - Steel labor suit, 1976
    - Miscellany, 1976-1977
  - Wechsler, James A., 1951-1971, (2 folders)
  - White House picketing restrictions, 1967-1969, 1976
  - Wiltse, Charles M., 1958-1960
  - Miscellany of briefs, writs, and committee prints (Box 132)
    - Ac-Ai, (4 folders)
    - Ak-Ama, (4 folders) (Box 133)
    - Ame-An, (4 folders) (Box 134)
    - An-Ara, (4 folders) (Box 135)
    - Arg-Au, (4 folders) (Box 136)
    - Av-Bay, (5 folders) (Box 137)
    - Bec-Boy, (4 folders) (Box 138)
    - Brad-Brot, (4 folders) (Box 139)
    - Brot-But, (4 folders) (Box 140)
    - Cab-Car, (3 folders) (Box 141)
    - Car-Char, (4 folders) (Box 142)
    - Char-Civ, (4 folders) (Box 143)
    - Civ (Box 144)
    - Civ (Box 145)
    - Civ-Cl, (3 folders) (Box 146)
    - Coi-Com, (4 folders) (Box 147)
    - Com-Coo, (4 folders) (Box 148)
    - Cot-Cros, (3 folders) (Box 149)
    - Crow-Da, (4 folders) (Box 150)
    - Da-Di, (4 folders) (Box 151)
    - Di-Elc, (4 folders) (Box 152)
    - Eld-Ex, (4 folders) (Box 153)
    - Fac-Fed, (3 folders) (Box 154)
    - Fed-For, (4 folders) (Box 155)
    - For-Ge, (4 folders) (Box 156)
    - Gi-Go, (4 folders) (Box 157)
    - Gol-Gra, (4 folders) (Box 158)
    - Gra-Gu, (3 folders) (Box 159)
    - Gy, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 160, Box 161)
    - Hai-Hel, (4 folders) (Box 162)
    - Hel-Hon, (4 folders) (Box 163)
    - Hon-In, (4 folders) (Box 164)
    - Int-Inv, (4 folders) (Box 165)
    - Ja-Jo, (4 folders) (Box 166)
    - Ju-Ka, (4 folders) (Box 167)
    - Ke-Kn, (4 folders) (Box 168)
    - Ko-La, (3 folders) (Box 169)
    - La-Lom, (3 folders) (Box 170)
    - Lon-Lu, (4 folders) (Box 171)
    - Mab-Mac, (4 folders) (Box 172)
    - Mac-Mar, (4 folders) (Box 173)
    - Marz-Mc, (3 folders) (Box 174)
    - Mc, (3 folders) (Box 175)
    - Me-Mil, (2 folders) (Box 176)
    - Mil-Mor, (3 folders) (Box 177)
    - Mor-Nat, (4 folders) (Box 178)
    - Ne-Ob, (3 folders) (Box 179)
    - Ob-Ol, (5 folders) (Box 180)
    - Ol-Peo, (4 folders) (Box 181)
    - Pet-Pl, (4 folders) (Box 182)
    - Pl-Pre, (4 folders) (Box 183)
    - Pri-Q, (3 folders) (Box 184)
    - Ra-Rei, (4 folders) (Box 185)
    - Rei-Rey, (4 folders) (Box 186)
    - Rh-Ru, (3 folders) (Box 187)
    - Sa-Sco, (4 folders) (Box 188)
    - Sco-Sec, (4 folders) (Box 189)
    - Sec (Box 190)
    - Sec-Ser, (3 folders) (Box 191)
    - She-Sil, (4 folders) (Box 192)
    - Sim-Ste, (4 folders) (Box 193)
    - Sto-Str, (4 folders) (Box 194)
    - Su-Ta, (4 folders) (Box 195)
    - Tea-Tr, (4 folders) (Box 196)
    - U-Vi, (4 folders) (Box 197)
    - Vo, (2 folders) (Box 198)
    - Vo-Wa, (4 folders) (Box 199)
    - Wa-We, (3 folders) (Box 200)
    - We-Wi (Box 201)
    - Wi-Y, (4 folders) (Box 202)
- Part I: Appointment Books, 1955-1986 (Box 203-212)
  Appointment books recording Rauh's personal and business activities.
  Arrangement is chronological.
  - 1955-1958 (Box 203)
  - 1959-1961 (Box 204)
  - 1962-1966 (Box 205)
  - 1967-1969 (Box 206)
  - 1970-1972 (Box 207)
  - 1973-1975 (Box 208)
  - 1976-1978 (Box 209)
  - 1979-1981 (Box 210)
  - 1982-1984 (Box 211)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 212)
- Part I: Miscellany, 1913-1989 (Box 212-216)
  Correspondence, memoranda, award certificates, articles, book reviews, interviews, photographs, speeches, newspaper clippings, printed matter, a scrapbook, and other material.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Awards and honors, 1971-1985 (Box 212)
  - Biographical articles and clippings, 1966, 1975-1988
  - Biographical file
  - Interviews
    - 1965-1967
    - 1969, 1978 (Box 213)
  - Invitations to speak, 1965-1970
  - Invitations to speak and correspondence re articles, 1959-1964
  - Scrapbook
    - Clippings
      - About others, 1942, 1974-1980
      - About Rauh
        - 1966-1985, (2 folders)
        - 1939-1948 (Box 214)
    - Correspondence, 1936-1946, 1964, 1976, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1913-1963, 1984
  - Speeches
    - By Rauh
      - 1950-1986, (4 folders)
      - 1989 (Box 215)
      - Undated
      - Speech notes
    - By others, 1989
  - Trip to New Zealand, 1974
  - Writings
    - By Rauh
      - Articles, 1948-1985, (5 folders)
      - Book reviews (Box 216)
        - Correspondence and notes, 1956-1986
        - General, 1940, 1949, 1975-1985
      - Law school papers, 1934-1935
      - Letters to editors, 1967, 1973-1986, (2 folders)
      - Newspaper articles, 1973-1986
      - Testimony and statements before various committees, 1967-1986
      - Miscellany, 1988
    - By others, 1948, 1958, 1964, 1984-1985
- Part II: Legal File, 1926-1988 (Box 217-268)
  Correspondence, memoranda, depositions, briefs, writs, petitions, transcripts, reports, medical records, and printed matter pertaining to the case Orlikow v. United States.
  Arrangement is alphabetical by type of material or subject.
  - Orlikow v. United States See also Containers 88, 274-282, and 287, same heading (Box 217)
    - Correspondence
      - Canadian government, 1977-1986, (4 folders)
      - Central Intelligence Agency, United States attorney and court, 1979-1985
      - General
        - July 1986-June 1988, (4 folders)
        - Sept. 1982-June 1986, (12 folders) (Box 218)
        - Sept. 1978-Feb. 1982, (4 folders) (Box 219)
      - Orlikow, David, 1977-1983
    - Memoranda, 1982-1985, (2 folders)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, media transcripts, 1979-1984
    - Clippings
      - 1987-1988, (2 folders)
      - 1949-1986, (8 folders) (Box 220)
    - Damages, 1988 (Box 221)
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Huard, Jeannine
      - Langleben, Florence
      - Logie, Robert K.
      - Orlikow, Velma
      - Page, Jean Charles
      - Stadler, Lyvia
      - Weinstein, Louis
      - Zimmerman, Rita
    - Depositions
      - Beauchamp, Tom, 1988, (2 folders)
      - Cameron, Duncan Hume, 1983
      - Cleghorn, Robert Allen, 1988
      - Desjardins, Juliette, 1988
      - Doyle, Brian B., 1988, (2 folders) (Box 222)
      - Duemling, Robert Werner, 1986
      - Gittinger, John W., 1983, (2 folders)
      - Goldman, Philip, 1983